what's up oh I hope the internet works
maybe it will god there's so much crap
about how you have to be like a prove to
stream on YouTube you know this is the
direction the tech companies are going
is we're gonna have a real stream who
remember Skokie Sunday back in the day
right and wait for some people to show
up I'll put on Twitter
let's go to Twitter I'd say here you to
come AI you know just like back in the
old days you guys still scobie's oh here
we go
my first hardware is canceled
come on
all right guys no nobody was seriously
castled away for a few people to get in
here I know no one even knew what the
new hardware was you know what guys I
was an idiot for announcing I
shouldn't have announced anything what's
up barn welcome to my youtube stream I
shaved a date last night I was thinking
you know it's a coming I archive yeah
that's cancel the new giraffe harness
whatever it was it's cancelled I'll show
you what we're thinking of do it instead
but then you know I have some
self-awareness got our self-awareness
you know I think this lacks a lot these
days all right
you only hear me good sound quality good
well iPhone eight over there like
alright good
look Oh excellent Oh perfect look see oh
you have a sound on our last video
but it's like it's me and I sit here
with my iPhone and it's good
um perfect so let's see what we're gonna
start with us um I watched my last the
last stream I did the last comment I
stream I did about the API Docs and I
hate it it disgusts me it's like we got
like like a legit like tripod and we had
talking points and like the comments
were like George you seem uncomfortable
like yeah cuz it's like once
once something is something like once
it's like a thing it's like I'm gonna
set up to do it right then there's
expectation and then it's not real
anymore
alright it can't be real it can't be
real once - this is real all right
I came in here today you know what I'm
doing you don't do when I'm around a
circuit board he wants to see the
circuit board I'm Riley right I got a
route circuit boards I'm pretty good at
it you know Oh
[Music]
and then I think back to the old
periscopes and I'm like well at least
they were real honest and genuine and
I'm gonna tell you guys something if the
ship sinks you know I'm gonna be real
about it and I'm gonna be honest about
it the new hardware didn't work
we got boards back those bugs um I don't
want to sell buggy hardware we never
sold buggy hardware before so it's
cancelled when it'll be done I don't
know we have to figure out this
decentralize all right we got to figure
out how to how to decentralize the
company right so here's some like ideas
that I have right you think that maybe
you know we can make open pilot run on
any phone um but this doesn't work this
doesn't work because you run into the
shipper problem you know we cancel
chipper are you running to the shipper
problem of people aren't gonna mount
phones I'll show you what we guys what
we're gonna make instead but you know I
look at them and they look shitty so you
know not actually gonna do it but like
here we go we've got some plastic Aeons
some miniature plastic Aeons
who wants a miniature plasticky on
miniature plasticy odds they didn't come
out that great stop them so we're not
even gonna sell me if you're black
jion's like tesla solve the miniature
plastic tesla
so yeah the hardware's canceled so if
you were thinking about like you know
not buying the car no hardware cuz the
new heart is coming out well there's no
more new hard right so also guys we got
it look we came out with the new website
right new website we think Oh new
website looks professional sales are
gonna go up well I mean I guess you
gotta be patient with these things but
sales ain't up so you know if sales
don't go up we can't we can't fund this
operation and I'm gonna be real with you
about that you know I was on I was on a
podcast hopefully it comes out soon I
was on a podcast last week and like
thank you yes all right I don't do a
great job I think the website looks
awesome
no we're not broke we're not broke we're
we're a start-up with runway right yes
that's that's that's the term for this
no the affiliate program had no effect
on sales at all I wish it did say also
not down there just the same
um I don't hear enough about comma
outside of what at what I'm gonna run
ants no one cares right um it's it's not
a competitive product really in the
modern world no not more advertising
right it's not a head which advertising
barely okay I could do like influencer
marketing or something you could market
end-users honestly if I stuck open pilot
on the devices told nishta I was gonna
do it would it really change anything I
can't make it work for old cars it's
impossible well it's not impossible but
you know you can look at X Matic trying
to do it if you had if you have to put a
motor on the steering wheel
you're gonna lose if I put a on on
Amazon I get more sales well that runs
into a few problem you know we put
pandas on Amazon once they got kicked
off Amazon for being too shitty I mean
it's not that they were too shitty it's
that the marketing was good and the
product was well a developer product
right so we're gonna making the product
better um I think I'm gonna be going to
China we're gonna get the new stuff
manufactured but you know a long time
from now I'm not doing Joe Rogan you
know again I had an opportunity okay
look at what happened after Elon did Joe
Rogan right like this is not where I
want to be in my life the world is kind
of toxic all right like the media is
toxic and I just like you think back in
the day you think back like money might
unlock the iPhone media it's like a nice
story they don't do that anymore the
media is just it's not that Elon wasn't
smart about it and and you know I feel
bad for the guy right like you know the
hate that he's gotten online recently
just just heard for bullsh
I know it's like but that's the best you
can hope for right the best you can
possibly hope for is to be is to be Elon
Oh like speeding will be better well I
just think oh I just think about that
yeah right um you know here so I was
talking about how open pilots open you
know and the car companies are here's
the real joke right anybody who thinks
they're like trying to license and make
money off of self-driving software we
are giving it away for free and open
pilot especially zero six which is still
coming out tomorrow is getting really
good and we can make it a lot better
we've built we've build great
infrastructure that you know we can
really just do it all the disengagement
is pretty much um you don't even know
hardware it can be done in the EON
platform you know cuz the problem of
self-driving is not a hardware promise a
software problem a better way that's
that's the other reason we can't do old
cars like you can't if you're trying to
build something mechanical that's gonna
go on a steering wheel you're giving it
away without the expertise right so you
think oh oh just go to the car companies
oh and then license it to them it's you
can't write to to understand like what a
car company is it's wrong to view it as
a person it's not like you can talk to
it
it's a it's a it's a massively
inefficient conglomerate super
intelligence and that's what these
companies are yeah you can put open
power on your Tesla it's its own look
yeah well I mean to say it's not a
person it's an entity and you can view
people as entities - it's it's an
intelligence
[Music]
yeah well Matt emphasized we're right
good luck this is why I left last year
you know after the 0.5 and the the press
push you know we did press last year it
was flawless
we did we did an hour of press on the
highway zero dis engagements the system
drove perfectly in the Civic um and I
realized that it almost doesn't matter
if it's perfect we can still do better
and like there's we can we can fix the
set of bugs we can start pushing on like
and make sure it doesn't take exit make
sure it stops or stopped cars get to red
lights or stop signs but I'm not sure it
matters it's not like you know get on
QVC does anyone still watch this right
you QVC is a scam it's not QVC is not
like a place you go to push here you
don't see iPhones for sale on QVC right
um at that point you're you're at that
point you've sold out and you know I'd
it's not worth it right in a way in a
way maybe maybe you know I can't win
because I'm not really willing to do
what it takes all right if what it takes
is selling out it's not worth it yeah
it'll work works great
what ml sets
it's for your morals it's not just that
it's it's not like stay true to your
morals right it's like the only thing
that makes any of this worth it is that
maybe the world's gonna get better maybe
the world's gonna move in a direction
where you know you say your products are
open-source right like there'd be a nice
direction for the world to move in
instead of instead of a small number of
people controlling the products that
billions of people use and you know you
you you see it I'm not going on Joe
Rogan you have to think of the personal
cost right I don't want that I don't
want that kind of attention what
hardware is gonna come out why is it
canceled if it was hardware it's
canceled so don't delay buying a neon if
we don't have enough sales in July we're
gonna pivot to being a boat company
we're gonna build one boat and I'm gonna
piece the out that's right thanks
VC's are we gonna build a boat one boat
well Don did it no the probably helped
the system do what it's perfect like III
fear that I fear that even if I made the
system like actually perfect it wouldn't
matter
yeah go on joe rogan get more sales
right personal cost I don't want to do
that it's not worth it and something I
don't like joe rogan I liked your rogan
um but the problem is okay so so once
something becomes mainstream it appeals
to a lowest common denominator audience
and it has to because well this is kind
of I think what happened to the internet
over the last ten years the internet
used to be this cool place
you know and they do is it's the reason
that a a a Facebook didn't exist
back then is because well it wouldn't
have appeal to the clientele of the
Internet you know think about just think
about it think about how far gaming has
fallen right think about world of
warcraft versus candy crush or Angry
Birds uh who was at the YC event I
didn't go I'm in San Francisco of course
no one knows ,
I'm not down though see I'm not down -
exactly I mean that is not exactly the
problem like you need more attention I
don't want to compete in the attention
economy I have no interest the attention
economy itself is a legitimate
what advice would I give to a CS grad
who's going into self-driving car as
well um I mean here's a cool thing it
probably doesn't even matter what we do
the technology is going to be
commoditized just as every so if you
believe that that uh every deep learning
breakthrough so far has been replicated
in a few months you know we have we have
we have replicas of alphago
we have replicas of GPT - everything
that comes out we have replicas pretty
soon because deep learning is a very
open field and there's no companies with
real monopolies on it even Google look
they made tensorflow open-source right
and you can say that oh there's there's
uh yeah what do I want to run Instagram
ads is that what I want to wake up and
do yeah we have more than 500 users um
there's like seven hundred daily actives
uh for $100 well you know the pro K so
now I sell it for $100 how much of that
is profit and then how many of those do
I have to sell and then how many cars do
I have to work with this model doesn't
even work at that kind of uh that kind
of scale um I'm running Instagram ad so
I'm gonna wake up in the morning and
check my Instagram ad board
like if I found some value aligned
influencers that's kind of different but
uh you'll make new hardware see but
alright so now I run into that problem I
don't want to be in the hardware
business I never wanted to be in the
hardware business but you can't do it on
a phone you can't do it on a phone and
we learned that I should start a YouTube
you mean a YouTube channel or a YouTube
competitor like bitch shoot yeah what no
but then what I'm a content
producer god yeah so we're working on
making the product better and easier to
set up I'm not even sure that actually
is the barrier to mass adoption in sales
it might have more to do with just
there's a reason no aftermarket products
succeeded on cars before and here's the
sad joke the sad joke of all of this is
we flex all of self-driving cars um but
it doesn't matter I like like it's if if
you're at the point where you're on the
highway and you have zero diss
engagements ah all right like like you
can't do better it's not a system that's
that says don't there's no no you kind
of -1 dis engagements right so you can
talk about a certain level of
reliability if it gets you to level 3 um
I mean we're we're a long way away from
that and there's going to be such a long
tail of absurd things because humans are
such good drivers well is it an
awareness problem that's a hypothesis or
is it a problem that just nobody really
cares um have we ever been approached by
car makers you there are no car makers
that can like approach you sure we've
had reach outs from car makers but it's
not like they're serious right like what
does it mean for a car maker to reach
out some low-level person and bizdev
reaches out I even spoke with the CEOs
of some of these companies and it's
there isn't really a path
forward unless you become mobilize
immobilized circa when was this date I
think was 2015 mobile I at the lowest
R&D spend of any chip manufacturer I'm
not getting bought out by the car
companies I'd rather sell to lyft or
uber oh it's not no ad the problem is
not the people are scared of the
technology the problem is that like the
machine that it would take to make this
successful
in today's world is so extremely
distasteful that I don't really want a
part of it right the machine that the
like advertising machine the marketing
machine that the you know I've come to
the new regulators I respect we were
making the Panda code mr. compliant the
hardware already follows at FMVSS you
don't remove your mirror anymore and
we're gonna justify our safety which i
think we're the only company in the
industry with an explicit definition of
what safety of level 2 looks like to
open piled safety md and yeah well
ground that in in ISO 26262 which is the
standard that the automakers use and
they're validating their cruise controls
no link assists I don't where comma
Marche anymore that's not you know I
could build high-end March and then it
might be cool what am i doing right now
I'm sitting on my computer I got a
router circuit board that's what I'm
doing
when is ml gonna play a bigger part what
do you mean by that we train your models
using ml whoa gang does an interesting
phase
yeah I'm from storage cheaper the clouds
of scam porting what vehicles we already
support all we already support 80% of
the vehicles it's possible to support
the problem is like oh sure we could add
Subaru support Nissan support but nobody
has Subarus and Nissan's right we added
we you know why the super giraffe was
canceled because we sold three of them
we sold three of them I made I made $200
I've had 60 bucks last night you know
out of dinner it's three dinners I got a
tip to rice it was three dinners HD man
so oh that's another one of those
companies all those HD map companies all
they're gonna be in for a drug that I
just failed you know I should be I
should be saying I told you so to
everybody right way to zooks fail yeah I
told you so I told you so
it doesn't matter um yeah maps have been
scrapped HD Maps in general aren't
really gonna be a thing most of the
value of HD maps has already been
captured by like super cruise and uh
sure the idea of precisely localizing
yourself in a map and then driving
according to it only solves the static
problem of driving and it turns out that
the static problem of driving is pretty
easy
in general the hard part is the well the
dynamic and the really hard part is the
counterfactual the counterfactual where
your actions affect other people's
actions like merging on the highway
merging is extremely hard I'm watching
weibo car try to merge right I'm not
sure you really can and code rules
you're gonna have to do reinforcement
learning and that's what people are
doing reinforcement learning out on the
road look we let kids drive man you know
yeah and he stalks a comma uh why don't
I start a digital identity startup and
address the billions of people oh my god
disgusted by that uh we're gonna be a
trusted source and authority what I
think of drive that a I think you felt I
mean but like you know I'm not even
hey look you know test Tesla
oh I can go pitch myself to youtubers hi
youtuber I'm down on my hands and knees
could you please review my product for
your stream I'll send you a free product
and I'll send you over and never mind
hookers and coke
are there roundabouts in the u.s. some
of them like yeah I'm standing out I'm
sending out what I'm sending out emails
to partner with media companies really
that my job which would run better if
you compare test autopilot with a pilot
it depends on the scenario open-mouth
better and some autopilot is better and
some auto pilot chooses to feel more
confident trading off being ok with
catastrophic failure versus open pilot
chooses to feel wobbly it's this is a
bunch of different trade-offs made in
autopilot an open pilot our torque
limits much lower not only because of
the cars just because I think that
Tesla's a little bit aggressive with
that Tesla's hardware is a lot better
than ours you know we have a phone in
the plastic case we don't have an office
in San Francisco we moved out
multi corner I don't know what that is
just got here what happened well the
July 1st hardware's canceled so you know
if you're waiting if you were waiting to
buy your Aeon for the new hardware
there's no more new hardware so you know
if you're gonna buy a neon via neon
hopefully sales go up right our Tesla
still making offers for you I haven't
heard from Tesla in 3 years no one's to
blame for the bad boards doesn't work
like that the companies to blame yeah
they're as verified can't run a can't
run yeah the EON de on isn't nearly
even in its limits of potential right
for example open pilots not that good
when you have like when you're coming up
with a stopped car at the radar vision
fusion this has everything to do with
the code and nothing to do with the
hardware when open pilot gets off an
exit this has nothing to do with the
hardware and everything to do with the
code
would open pilot pulls you aggressively
into a left turning lane this has
everything to do with the code nothing
to do with the hardware no see but the
twitch see if the twitch became a thing
I just wouldn't want to do it anymore
it already kind of became a thing is
everything good what do you mean by that
all I can promise you guys is I'm gonna
go out honestly that's right
yawn really only helps lateral movement
well it depends on the car some of the
cars have good longitudinal some of them
have terrible longitudinal like the
Civic stock longitudinals way worse than
the Aeons oh the new hardware it's not
it's not a neon it was never gonna be a
neon replacement anyway can the new
hardware be community produce like the
pedal mm too complex look if we couldn't
get it right then I don't know about a
open sourcing if the pedal was simple we
already had pedals any plastic Aeons who
wants to buy a mini plastic healing what
was the new hardware anyway the new
hardware was mini plastic eons but they
don't look very nice
so we cancel them roll call may I have
in 10 years probably none most out of
sale
what channel would source everything god
I'd open source the back end I mean if I
thought someone could use it and I
thought that the value would be captured
by people and not by entities well
there's no point in talking about what
it was because well it's canceled so and
then like we're gonna do like a fake
event tomorrow where it's like oh we're
gonna win ounce plastic Aeons and like
it's funny at first when you think about
it but then you realize like wow okay
look up intel the odyssey right if you
want if you want something to laugh
about
oh please consider ah now I'm a magnetic
sticker manufacturer really ship black
rain to 21 million people in a week and
now I make magnetic stickers that 26
people are gonna buy pathetic you don't
need more care you don't even really
need more cameras we're not even nearly
at the limit of the EON camera for
example cut-ins
alright when cars cut you off the e on
camera can see this fine the problem is
it's just not in the field of view or
vive there the model or the radar right
we can fix that
it's don't challenge and left driving
countries we could just care about it
the problem is we have like 20 users
right so let's see 20 users maybe a
lifetime user value of calm AI is like
$500 so 20 times 500 that's $10,000
right so I can devote maybe one
engineering month to it that's the
problem all right
no it doesn't detect gardens haifa
Tesla's battery event you know what it's
gonna be
I gotta promise something they're gonna
be like kind of there and yeah you all
probably win at the end of it is open
sourcing everything really a good
business decision well keeping some of
it closed wasn't a good business
decision so at least you know with open
source there's a legacy right
why not flip the camera out but you mean
flip it like that um so we've discussed
that uh I don't know maybe it works
iPhones are dying sell the company -
what - losers why have a merchandise
section on the store I don't know
something I guess I guess cause it kind
of made sense so okay with open sourcing
we have a lot of people contributing for
free a to an extent um the truth about
the truth about open sourcing is you
then you then just become a manager
right like a lot of times I'd rather a
lot of times I'd rather write code then
have to manage external people writing
code that's like bad all right like like
there is there is almost more overhead
than just writing some of the code
myself we've gotten some good open
source contributions but the idea that
like this can be developed organically
is not really true and you can read the
open pilot commit history for that I
even merging in a fingerprint takes like
an hour of an engineering engineer's
time here um Bosch killed the Civic for
kamma used to be the best car why cuz
boss doesn't have longitudinal shall we
do it we could do it is that gonna fix
things probably not the Toyota cool is
the best car if you're buying a new car
for open pilot definitely by the the
2020 Corolla you can argue that Bosch
stock is kind of better than Vostok is
quite good I mean yeah we can improve it
let me know Android auto what's that
mean Oh Toyota has no Android auto yeah
I know you finally ordered the open
pilot it arrives tomorrow was that a
mistake you know why was it invited to
be a mistake works like it does it works
pretty well what will grey pandas be
used for now well if you have a great
panel your data's included in the model
I mean all right Doug feels that way
about Corollas yeah yeah one murder two
one wears you out back what other
projects I know it's amazing
doesn't matter though
yeah what's the bike column I'll give
you a good price awful I think he
promised that he was gonna have a fleet
of level 5 taxis by the end of the year
right if only I could go on augur and
short that can't though
can't and that's the problem you know
this is a general a general sort of like
media problem in general the the
accusation is printed in huge in huge
texts or the claim is printed in huge
headlines and then the follow through or
lack thereof is printed in a little a
little line down at the bottom you want
being full of it right like like it's
like you know people who thought Trump
was gonna change after he became
president he's the same guy right like
Elon just cuz he lands Rockets like this
now it's pretty incredible achievement
right like he's not gonna change he's
always gonna make these these that's
just who he is as a person right he's
always gonna make these claims that will
someday will you on have a level 5 taxi
network you probably will
I still think Tesla's gonna win even be
at the point now where open pilot like
oh my god Elon called me in my birthday
you see this just it's a narrative thing
right like it doesn't like like that's
not it's not even that it's not true
right and that's what a lot of fake news
is it's not that the news itself is
wrong it's that the narrative is kind of
misleading right
Elon calling me and my birthday is a
it's like a red herring kind of thing it
doesn't mean anything right but you say
it because it creates a compelling
narrative the Elon is the Aeons were
selling right now our lake all the pro
threes yeah I mean welcome to hoarding
for an Elon company in the pace office
the yards are double but you're
contributing on a mission to make the
world better
some people that's worth it is long
improved no maybe a little
maybe targeted niche abusers yeah we're
8.1 million dollar VC back startup you
think I can you think I can target
initial users right sound of doing with
my life a car path you might have ever
having just did a new lose like ICML
talk is pretty good what features can
you look forward to know more features
we're not doing features you can look
forward to some stability uh-oh
oh great oh I'm gonna saw the outback PR
I'm gonna I'm gonna sell me to sell to
more yonce oh oh my god two more eons
yeah you make tacky minigames right yeah
why don't we sell many plastic eons
right no I'm not gonna start a cult
jailbreaking reality because I gave that
talk and the only people who reached out
to me we're quacks and schizophrenic and
that's the problem right you can't you
can't make any claim like that because
it's like if you ask the people in the
office whether they want to use sequel
or no sequel for the database solution
no one really cares nobody has an
opinion on that because nobody can
understand it but if you ask them what
color they want to paint the wall that's
what we're gonna have a two-hour meeting
for right someone needs to fix messaging
what's wrong with messaging right
messaging was was pretty good back in
the day oh oh yeah oh I'll just all work
out it'd be a mutually beneficial
partnership you scratch my back I'll
scratch yours
I'm just not like I can't tolerate the
right shippers dead she wanted
an open source that if anyone really
cares no I won't open source it's not
gonna help people it's only gonna help
ya shippers been dead for a while oh you
know what I can plug this into you know
what I'm gonna plug my iPhone into the
charge I'm gonna plug it into a panda
orientation is locked rotate device back
I know I'll call the wall be painted
panda perfect yeah so you know what
we're gonna do we're gonna try
what do you mean is funding drying up we
have the same funding we always had like
you get more if I cared as Talent drying
up no we have the same talent we always
had we're better at using it now but it
just maybe just structurally doesn't
work um comedians work right three C's
hate me um yawns make a nice they make a
nice side business they put good money
in my pocket they could fund a great
lifestyle for me you know you can really
do this as far as I can tell as far as I
can tell you know the VCS on equity not
debt um so you could just decide that
your company is gonna be a lifestyle
company pay yourself I mean you couldn't
pay yourself a million dollar your
salary even if you want to pay yourself
you know 250 K you can justify that
pretty easily called a nice lifestyle
business keep it going and yeah hey yeah
you could do that right oh can i
elaborate on that board oh I'll finish
routing it yeah please a little trace in
place right that's great that you
believe in commenting on makes uh you
know one of us um no it's not that
I think no one really wanted this you
know you guys do what peak self-driving
cars was you guys know what yeah you
ever go on Google Trends and look up
self-driving car kind of funny
keek of self-driving cars floating oh
yes oh yes yes you see that peak that
was when Hoover killed somebody
that was the peak of self-driving cars
humans are banned from driving oh yeah
yeah you know what just really I don't
know what to do about this
I think he'll one person yeah oh yeah
Alain Herzberg we all know her name
right um it's not nobody is punished for
hype like if you go back and you watch
all right real talk real talk
if you go back and watch my TechCrunch
Disrupt I said to my sister a week
before I'm like what I really want to do
is go up there and take a dump on the
stage right I just want to take a
pull my pants down take a right um
so you can't actually do that right I
think that would be a little bit too
obvious so I tried to do it verbally and
metaphorically but what people saw was
not a mockery of hype but hype itself if
you're truly dumb enough to believe that
a piece of green 3d printed plastic is
the solution to self-driving cars then I
can't help you right like like if you
are dumb enough to believe that then how
can you be critical at all about any
other Heidi claim right you're not
nobody is
and like it's you know it's Crowley and
daraprim right like the guys like look
you know I took this one obscure drug
that nobody uses and I jacked the price
massively on everyone books it shkreli
is the bad guy but the only reason they
look at shkreli is the bad guys because
the language he uses the truth is the
pharmaceutical industry is doing that
every day just to like less of an
extreme right and they couch it in like
lawyer resounding language and you know
nobody really sees it for what it is
right so shkreli is in jail for eight
years and the guy who uh you know
marketed oxy to the kids as uh this all
had to pay a six hundred million dollar
fine Oh Purdue Pharmaceuticals is gonna
go broke right sure sure you could right
but here's the thing about your tech
your tech you want you want to save
people's lives
you want to reduce car accidents you
save five people's lives to kill one hmm
what is the world focus on what does the
news focus on what are the people focus
on do I inspire the hype looking Paul
the death Vigo never ends I put it now I
like her I like to tweet is like a
milestone is the thing that doesn't make
headlines right like one of those one of
those truck companies one of the worst
ones not embark
oh we drove a truck down the highway
with no person in it for the first time
all right they had leaden Ihnen and then
chase cars with people in them but like
it's not that's not a milestone right
but it doesn't matter because Ford is
partnering with Domino's to use
self-driving cars for pizza the Lemery
right you need to take advantage of a
bunch of fools right if that's why it's
my panda not charging my iPhone if I
need to take advantage of a bunch of
fools if that's really what it's gonna
take then I'm not down not down not down
anyone figure how to plug this in
it's not my computer I'm gonna lose my
computer if I do that oh no these eons
are flat these pandas are flat with
different firmware so they don't charge
phones anymore I'm gonna go get a new
pan
anyone want to buy pandas I got a lot of
them panda buy a panda made 10,000 over
oh that's unplugged now great plug that
back in turn this on there we go now I
can park my iPhone it
what do you mean no new features are
coming I didn't say that
well no new features are coming
stability is coming 0.6 comes out
tomorrow people like it
thousands shipped like 5,000 pandas or
some
I didn't make autopilot you got the
wrong guy
oh oh you want to look at logs from
explores last year I got some bad news
for you we keep the data around for
about 30 days you know why because
someone's got to pay the cloud down all
in clouds expensive oh yeah free date
all right is Tesla gonna win all right
so you get into Tesla right look at
Tesla's stock fell massively right does
that mean Tesla's doing badly no it just
means didn't live up to the hype and
that's again the problem they created
hype for themselves and brought their
stock to an unsustainable level where
Tesla was valued at more than Ford and
then you realized wait a second nobody
actually buys model threes in the f-150
is the top-selling car in the country
all right all right guys um we'll go for
an hour so we got we got 15 more minutes
that's today's livestream we're keeping
it real I don't know how much the stocks
really related to how are you on tweets
um no so yeah we're not doing features
anymore features aren't really what you
want what you want a stability and user
friendliness we tried features we tried
maps they were janky remembers our
feature features removed how would I ran
companies doing autonomy today like
don't get me started on way moe like
there is no way they're gonna ever
recoup the twenty billion dollars they
put into that thing Uber's never gonna
recoup it at all can't believe all the
money blown on that uber has nothing
they have less than nothing they have a
dead person right and nothing to show
for it
um Weibo has something but you know how
are they gonna recoup 20 billion dollars
for it I don't see it so yeah how how
our company's doing well try open pilot
the only thing that beats at his auto
pilot in certain scenarios
Apple Apple bought the remnants of a
failed self-driving company but that's
not what you see in that aligns right
yeah someone should do walking in VR
well no you see you want features
because the system is stable enough a
lot of the people who buy a lot of
people who don't buy Aeons are not not
buying because they're waiting for a
feature they're not buying because it
looks like a hobbyist product because
you know it takes 20 minutes to compile
and you get random black screens and
sometimes your panda light flashes green
these are the things we're fixing and
and what you'll find is that in order to
succeed in order to succeed with any
sort of market you don't want a lot of
features that kind of work you want one
feature that works extremely well
why can't we have traffic light and stop
sign stop and go that's not what you
want like you think that's what you want
but it's a gimmick the truth is you know
what you'd probably much prefer when
there's already a car stopped at the red
light wouldn't you like to be able to
stop for that right now it's hit or miss
now it works sometimes you don't want
that so we'll fix that
it's a dev device though not a consumer
product see this is what I mean and
maybe I just don't understand how people
think about the world there's no
difference all right well it's a deaf
device and not a consumer product
I mean it's rough around the edges we're
working on cleaning that up at what
point does it stop being a deaf device
had become a consumer product when I
change the couple of lines on the
website and start shipping them with
open pilot don't think it changes
anything all right can you yeah people
can use it over consumers if you're
willing to put time McCullar right and
that time is what we're trying to reduce
so like okama is not doing anything
you're not doing any new features no
we're gonna work on like for example the
green flashing light of the pant is
about to be gone in 0-6
the models are much better in zero sex
I'm not playing the profit maximization
game if Moloch kills me Moloch kills me
kodaline this tech tips again what did I
tell you about begging youtubers
youtubers come to me you know what I'll
say shop comm that I buy any on review
it give me your honest opinion right
this isn't gonna be some sketch backroom
deal like I shouldn't have to go to
anybody if they want to review it they
can review it if they don't they won't
write well why is this why does this
have to be centralized and not
decentralized uh yeah until it plugs in
place oh we're getting there
we're getting there you know a lot of
the stuff that you think it's like it's
not typing in open pilot comma that I on
the URL screen shipper is completely
dead and there's never gonna be updated
again
um can your mom set up IKEA furniture or
install a GPU that's probably gonna be
the bar until oh you sell it in
dealerships right you build a product
you can sell in dealerships Wow I go to
the dealership so I'm gonna walk down to
the dealership I it's Fred eggs my boy
Fred you know um no no because it's
below me I'm not saying that what I'm
saying is like that's not who I am or
anything I want to be associated with
right I don't be a brand and it's not
like oh why don't you hire somebody to
handle the branding component yeah
that's my boy
yeah well we'll see about sales but no
we're working on improving all compiled
quality that's exactly what we're
working on
you should be more open to opportunity
for the company not yourself what do you
mean by that what is the company
corporations are people my friend
nope the sources aren't gonna be
released it's cuz I'm an asshole that's
why all people will trust the dealership
own good you'll be able to update
compound self updates turn it yell off
and on again it just updates oh the
visualization of the HTML shows your
simulator I have a simulator now imagine
Sony doing soft I agree
well you should trust what's
statistically verified to drive your car
what time is zero six going live
tomorrow oh no well you want to know the
truth we have a meeting at 11:00 I'm
gonna be like I'm gonna say to Yelp I'll
team a you want to push zero six and
they'll be like okay well pushes your
sex my coding a streamline I don't feel
like doing coding streams anymore I'm
playing online chess badly
what about porting the EON to work on
any phone well the problem with that is
people don't want to mount their phones
on the dashboard how are they gonna
mount it stapling what are we gonna do
when that phone has some weird process
that you installed because the Android
has spyware all right can you buy shares
in the company don't for private do I
not believe in it anymore well you have
to know you have to tell me what you
mean by that right
like I guess I believe the same thing I
believe for the last couple of years if
the success of kamma AI is a function of
my belief in it something is seriously
wrong but I fear cava will fall behind
fall behind oh we're years ahead it
doesn't matter though right like like
years ahead in a race that like at least
we have some revenue right way Mo's
years ahead they've never made a dollar
uh now I'm president now it's like being
CEO except you know you don't have to
like put on a good face you can just say
whatever the hell you want cuz you're
president right as I learned that from
our president just say whatever you want
man uh we're not here to talk about me
this is on the cob AI channel just like
we don't talk about comm a I on my
twitch channel right see it's all
complete push me the water in the middle
of the Atlantic I mean look it's not
like it's not like oh it's not like I
point to somebody else and they're doing
better I mean maybe the company doing
best in the space is like not oh you
could do that you won't do that somewhat
honest business model
[Music]
the older car question I've answered
that a bunch of times not gonna happen
oh there's no main takeaway there's no
action items it's just an hour-long rant
that's all it is I just thought that you
I that's not simple enough it's that
there's a lot of subtlety that's wrong
and yeah I think you can and I think
that's what working to improve and I
think that's what the zero six here is
gonna be about just flying Jones for
wheat delivers don't pitch it doesn't VC
somewhere I don't know what an eye cave
body system is the own poly UI we just
open sourced it so there's a bunch it's
it's partially in sea and partially in
react native this is a bunch of apk is
calming I open pilot apk and then
there's you I dot see in the main open
pilot repo oh yeah well so one of the
one of them off-road is written in react
native and then frame is written in
Colin what about six again you know what
I mean how may I could be profitable
zooks
I don't see how you ever make back the
billions you've spent I don't think you
can not weaponizing man oh oh can I
put forward to education all yeah you
know what I always say you know what I
always say to people it's not my job to
educate there's tons of great resources
out there if you can't figure out how to
educate yourself I don't know what to
say um II on be a dash cam with safety
functions oh oh that sounds like a
terribly boring product we warn you when
the driving is unsafe
like yeah yeah you could build that
sounds boring and then why you got to
sell safety
I thought that safety is not good safety
is great but like you know what cell
safety I like you sell like oh this
makes driving safer it just reminds
people how dangerous driving us Oh
Malcolm is quite readable I think I
don't know we can refactor it I want to
work on that we're gonna work to make it
better
Jay Lord welcome to the streams
I think Aisha Evans got put in the
rubber room at Intel for tanking their
modem division you didn't hear that from
you know what I say love Elon Musk
offered me 400 million yeah
depends will you let me keep it open
source ifs others sure it's all for less
than that if you'd let me keep it open
source if he says you got to make it
close source and we're basically just
buying you to kill open pilots a lotta
pilot born of any competition give me a
billion dollars sick now what am I
gonna do with money buy I'm
gonna buy some cardio bracelets i'ma buy
Louie Vuitton bag buy more Saint Laurent
hoodies is Python the best tool for AI
programming sure cuz tensorflow works
with that ten smells like heavily bound
to Python they Swift now as a layer on
top of Python it's kind of cool
well cars aren't gonna be shipped with
good a TAS for a long time for two
reasons one they have no connectivity to
get the data back and two they have no
ability to OTA update when they fix bugs
those two things are probably really not
gonna be done until 2025 at the earliest
so you're looking at six years before
they can be remotely competitive I mean
it's a bit of work now but if we have
the tech to make it I mean you know
we've been collecting data now for three
years we have huge infrastructure
designed to process them but you see the
problem with like sending them info like
is this my job now is it my job now to
like raise awareness all let's raise
awareness why don't we start a campaign
why do we have a self-driving awareness
to her oh we tried that
Oh joke man no new hardware actually
legit is cancelled by the old harder if
you want you sold them pilot we didn't
hire a market I wouldn't hire our
marketer the whole thing is disgusting
right like why our designer it will make
websites look nicer hey that's that's
engineering
empathy ain't your thing you tell me
what empathy means man you tell me what
it means did you talk about school
shootings on here again he would be
banned from this channel
yeah exactly right so don't tell me I
don't have something if you can't define
it probably I mean the way empathy is
used a lot it's a scam right it's a form
of it some way you can control people's
behavior right you could say like well
you shouldn't do that you should have
more empathy you shouldn't buy Clorox
you should have more empathy and by dawn
you know it's a thing that you're
supposed to have but wait was that just
an ad for dawn
tailored you're about to get banned a
lot of people on here get OH
put user a timeout Oh get bad I love it
you know come AI his new slogan is make
driving chill
alright guys who spent an hour thank you
the new websites nice let's hope it
improves sales
education its biggest scam in history
guys of course it's marketing right why
don't we mark it it'll give your
children a future to the parents and
it's a four year party to the kids and
government pays for all the debts and
though I love education scam yes be
honest I'm not snot my job no one voted
for me to make America shut down so it's
not my job
san Diego's are right
how many aeons have been sold a lot but
not enough ah thank you thank you ok
trying to hope you enjoy my stream today
we're keepin it real if I ever try to
you be like George I can tell
you're trying to me like if I
was gonna try to sell you plasticky
aunts tomorrow is tempting me trying to
you but if you want to buy a
plasticy on they're not for sale they're
exclusive they're extremely rare with
these little plastic eons on my desk not
being on joe rogan thank you what is
this dream for it's to tell you all the
hardware's canceled you should go shop
that comment buddy i invite you right
now come on come on get my sails up make
me happy you know i come in in the
morning I checked my Shopify if sales
are big I'm happy if sales are small I'm
unhappy
I don't even agree well you got a virtue
a signal to some losers that you like
you know sat somewhere for four years
and paid a boatload of money
yeah yeah right you could do that if you
want but then you're in a system of
losers take view see you money like Elan
see that's the difference right
Elan thinks there's some greater purpose
to it all you on thinks that like
the ends justify the means I don't know
I don't I don't have a degree
come on info voice Oh God
dan from youtube don't and you said the
i-word VC's help push you VC is help
push you toward annual recurring revenue
in surveys are you're doing it up
consumer surveys you know have you
noticed that everything is now it's got
a survey a survey a survey create a GI
to rule the worlds here I like that plan
I like that plan I think the Chinese are
gonna beat us all to it I not make the
community my sales force I tried it
we had a very generous affiliate program
didn't do he sees capitalism human
centered capitalism right yeah I mean if
capitalism becomes this long term
capitalism is great short term
capitalism and like we got to make sure
we impress the guys on Wall Street next
quarter yeah that's why we live in the
world today right am i a socialist or
capitalism
I am capitalism I am Queens Boulevard
right um I need made voting machine that
votes for you yeah what if we just made
voting machines and we figured out how
to use AI to vote so we can cut the
voter out of the equation right audio
out a thing now alright that's a perfect
time to end the stream all right thank
you all thank you all for watching
is the audio back in sync already done
what AI voting machine without the voter
honey I girlfriend I love I'd love to
have an AI girlfriend you guys my audio
is a nice thanks it's been it's been 64
minutes unless my phone's lying to me
you try to get more time
make some joke about hookers and
therapists I'd like to send my dignity
to you
no I don't want to take off a non-3d
girlfriend real smart you know real
smart go
hey what's the solution to lack of sales
you all gonna buy mine I don't know
we're gonna make it easier to use we're
gonna make this thing great even just
for the sake of making it great I'm
gonna do it
after markets humble heading for rockets
yeah really hit Ilan where it hurts man
hey you got your you got your Atlas you
got your your your Atlas five rocket
just just stick a neon in it it'll land
itself think about all the money you'll
save
thank you for our moment
proofs of car computers I like the
tittie printer maker come get the angle
there is no end goal stream rap new rap
oh maybe no you can't tap into the stock
camera this is not how good the same bad
ideas get repeated over and over and
over again look at the pin outs of the
stock camera and see if there's any way
you can get the picture a trick no you
get some shitty post process outputs
pushes the reason your car drives badly
with the stock camera in the first place
so we hear that bad idea a lot and we
hear the idea why don't you make it work
with all cars oh you know I never
thought of that before I never thought
of that before the only reason I make it
work with the cars I do make it work
with is because I'm a dick and I don't
like the other cars you know it's just a
way of like you know getting one out and
poor people right if I knew car man what
are you poor oh there's a young work
with the stock camera we leave the stock
camera enabled now we're soon gonna like
proxy a V and stuff thank you please any
more live streaming no this this was a
special treat I was feeling some type of
way you know some type of way
yeah oh yeah making work on tricycles
that's a big market you know there's a
lot on tap market I get those kids man
get those kids you know we'll put in our
Sock'em boppers sock about buying Eon
for your tricycle why did you send you
go out into San Diego man so right now
San Francisco sucks all right come on
yeah we'll be around here for 30 years
don't be buying me on sevens now you
really want to make money today jewel
look they made a lot of money just take
something that's addictive and repackage
it in a new farm um well I like on my
pizza pepperoni not San Francisco yeah
okay like BAM jewel there oh yeah you
want to buy a cigarette so that's fine
but you want to buy jewel yeah we kind
of get kids drooling and vaping man it's
messing with the kids man do I consider
pineapple a legitimate topping it's not
the topping I would choose but it is it
is legitimate I don't question the
legitimacy of piden how do we get out of
the simulation yeah I could forward you
a bunch of crackpot is from people you
want to hear like a 14 page essay about
like you know how the Illuminati is is
conspiring with the license plate
manufacturers to put the letters in them
yeah wqr I learn how to examine and exit
the simulation yeah I see you know what
in San Francisco we had cars broken into
three times three times we had cars
broken into the office was broken into
once the amount of clunk that city is
now the highest crime city in America
for for non non violent crime in some
cities that are more violent but when it
comes to like like like property crimes
San Francisco's the highest in the
country all right CY to get out right
damn right damn so don'ts kind of downs
like with the with the weed in the other
the the blowtorch smoke to dab once what
did i watch i watch some i watched some
like television show it wasn't Rick and
Morty it was like like Family Guy or
some I just laid on the couch like long
watching watch your family guy dab on
the haters right Oh dad like that like
that yeah yeah yeah I was down again
then I'm straight and sorry and if
you're if you're female you know to
email me but I do know that 93% of my
audience is male I've looked into my
demographics well then and then uh you
know you know me but ya never missed the
iPhone jailbreaking stuff you can't know
what it's not it's not there's no one
well guys I do know that 93% of you were
men okay that's all I know I'm just
saying I'm looking at my demographics we
need to increase diversity and inclusion
on the cob a on YouTube channel
what's hire a chief diversity officer to
do that um no I've never been to South
Africa here there's a lot of crime
wearing like young guy giraffe be sold
to all seven yonder users we have a few
more than 70 and I users yes we have HR
absolutely and my tolerance for
is zero you want to like do some
like some harassment
get the out um
right and that's you know how it should
be you know the Linux go to contact this
is you know the fact that we're even
talking about that right and that's the
real problem these people just like they
monopolize discourse to say nothing to
say things that are either so obvious
harassment is bad you know um and
then they monopolize discourse you know
like but but how bad is it
right why do we even pay for office
space oh thank you like the API why we
even pay for office space that's a good
question should decentralize the company
we don't go remote maybe we'll do that
um what business model I don't care
whatever code of conduct is lame or not
just like you know if it makes some
people happy put it in there and like
you don't have to read there right like
who cares
don't let these things get to you man
gasp go remote no go go over mode new
office space Starbucks we'll work it we
works right like the Millennial children
we are which business model we'll sell
you all car insurance right is that a
good business model sell-off seven
hundred users car insurance well no cuz
only like four hundred then were in the
US and then I know you can't sell health
insurance across state lines I don't
know about car insurance but I think
we're in video now yeah and then you did
something to me last year they kind of
like screwed me over
I sold half my Nvidia stock I really
wish I sold it all cuz it was the peak
fidgety what is the Instagram followers
I was somewhat serious about that you
have to have an Instagram these days
it's gonna go on dates you know girls
text you they're like what's your
Instagram got a man Instagram
this is another myth that like driver is
like I get this about India a lot like
you just got a tree money media drivers
then you learn how to like really drive
know if you want to train a model that
drives in Pittsburgh you train on
Pittsburgh drivers you want to train a
model that drives in South Africa
traveled South African drivers right
that seems very clear to me Nvidia it
wasn't always this way they started like
you know believe in their own
videos I really what I should have sold
all my Nvidia stock was the minute they
added that thing to the License
Agreement
where you can't use the gaming GPUs and
data centers like really can't use it
for that the second a company tries to
put like restrictions on how you can use
the product legal restrictions not
technical restrictions it's not even
like it's not like like it's like okay
fine you want to put it you know a legal
restriction again it's like piracy fine
but like this isn't even an intellectual
property thing this is just protecting
your ability to upsell losers am do you
gonna beat Intel well we'll see um Intel
Intel has made a lot of bad decisions
where's the ten nanometer chips right
yeah yeah NVIDIA banned you from using
gaming GPUs in data centers to protect
their their their ability to upsell
their higher product that's gross
I'll just wait seven days nvidia did
more stupid things until missed the
mobile market a long time ago Nvidia
missed the molten market the mobile
market is dominated by Qualcomm and
Apple and then like okay you got
Kieran's over there and you got got
Samsung but that's that's really just
about it
yeah no I hear I hear this is that a new
is that the old rise in our new rising
Thank You Howard I learned to code I
climbed down to the bottom of an
Indonesian volcano and found this source
of coding scroll the scroll of coding
ability and I read it but I drew it into
the sulfur check it out the volcano is
called ijen why not manufacture in the
USA where I'd love to I'm a big America
fan but when I can pay people in China
$2 an hour
no I burned the scroll I burned the
scroll we can't let we can't let future
generations get access to the forbidden
knowledge i gen ije at google it it's a
volcano Indonesia where I found the
skull of scroll of big coding ability
thoughts on risk 5 risk architecture is
gonna change everything man what movies
at home I don't know whether to ban
hitting on me in the channel it might
get banned I'll give a warning this is
about your good
we don't have to go that far the mute
streamer no-risk architecture is gonna
change everything it's an Angelina Jolie
line in hackers hey Nathan Levin douse
kill you related to anthony levin dosti
by chance robotic process automation
yeah the robots are coming for your job
yang 2020 damn I wanted these at home
too
nice key points oh yeah yep get old
people like them yeah man the boomers
got please the boomers man could be
beneficial to do more wait I just got a
text I wonder what it says but if I
click on it I think my stream will stop
um like Genesis like Sega Genesis
Hyundai Genesis Genesis is a separate
brand now right yeah it works it works
at the owns what successful tech company
would you say calm areas boss like well
uh you know and they make good no it's
like not just sex BOTS but love man love
Jack love Tech is gonna is gonna be the
next revolution get an early on love
tech all right like you think you guys
think it's like weed stocks and like
whatever else is hot today love tech
tensorflow
hey levin dosti look at pronto ai
they're literally just copy comma right
like it's the right idea it's just a
question of how much patience you have
um yeah if it still likes a comma yeah
yeah I went to the bottom of I Jenna I
found the skull of Cole's bowl of amends
coding ability
yeah catgirls us definitely
rust this fun but not practical go was
boring put a very practical language
some of the people who work here better
than me at some things alright alright
streams over thank you guys once week
once we get into programming language
debates
that's what shoes over thanks power how
do you deal with self-confidence you
don't ask that question you just have it
seven simple steps to raising your
self-confidence by